https://www.johnfdoherty.ie/index.php/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy of John F. Doherty and The Beehive School
John F. Doherty and The Beehive School operate the www.johnfdoherty.ie website, which provides users with information on activities, services and events
and the ability to book courses, workshops, retreats and training as well as
purchase
online, these actions are
heretofore referred to as our Service / Services.
This page is
used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the
collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information when anyone
decides to use the Services offered on johnfdoherty,ie’s website.
If
you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use
of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information
that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We
will not use or share your information with anyone except as described
in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection and Use
For
a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to
provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including
but not limited to your name, phone number, and postal address. The
information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.
Log Data
We
want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect
information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This
Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet
Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you
visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages,
and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are
files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous
unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that
you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Our
website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve
our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these
cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you
choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions
of our Service.
Service Providers
We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
To facilitate our Service;To provide the Service on our behalf;To perform Service-related services; orTo assist us in analysing how our Service is used.
We
want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access
to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks
assigned to them on our behalf. They, the data processors, use the data
only as The Sanctuary, as data controller, instructs them. They are
obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
We use a trusted third party to host our website and securely store email communication. You can find the Hosting Ireland Privacy Policy here.
We use a trusted third party to manage our email newsletter subscription. You can find the Mailchimp Privacy Policy here.
Our website uses a Facebook Tracking Pixel and Google Analytics tracking
to improve site performance and your experience on the site. Where
possible we anonymise data collection, including your IP address with
Google Analytics.
Security
We value your
trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to
use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that
no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic
storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its
absolute security.
Links to Other Sites
Our
Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party
link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites
are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the
Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume
no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any
third-party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our
Services do not address anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly
collect personal identifiable information from children under 18. In
the case we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with personal
information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a
parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us
with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to
do necessary actions.
The right to be forgotten
Any
individual about whom we store information may, on request, demand to
remove any and all information that we have stored about them. Please
make all “Right to be Forgotten” requests by email to info@thebeehive.ie
in accordance with current GDPR legislation we will complete all Right
to be Forgotten requests within 30 days of receiving them.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We
may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to
review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of
any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These
changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us info@thebeehive.ie
